All right. Hello, everybody. Welcome.
Um so, if you watched my previous video
on how to run ComfyUI through RunPod,
this is the direct follow-up video. And
this is how you will be getting your
first workflow running. This is a pretty
good workflow. Um it works
very well. Um I created it myself. Um
and if you want to get it, all you have
to do is get in my Discord. It's free in
there, 100% free. All you got to do is
join. There is a
text channel called free workflows, and
I even have a written-out guide, a short
guide, on how to do this in that
channel, as well.
So, assuming you just downloaded it, and
you have it here,
you are going to drag it into ComfyUI,
and you're going to see
a few error messages.
So, first you're going to see that you
have missing nodes, which this is very
simple to solve. First of all, what you
want to do is go to the manager up here.
Just press the blue manager button.
And then you're going to click install
missing custom nodes.
Now, the missing nodes will appear right
here, and they will have install
buttons. You need to do this one by one.
So, you're just going to click install.
You're going to wait for that to go
through, and then it's going to tell you
that you need to restart ComfyUI. But
before you do that, just install the
rest of the missing nodes, and then
you're going to restart.
So, once those are installed,
restart. It's going to ask you if you're
sure. Yes, and now we just wait for
Comfy to restart.
All right. Once the restart has fully
reloaded, it's going to ask if you want
to refresh. Just click confirm and
refresh ComfyUI.
All right. Now, we should not have any
glowing red nodes. But if you try and
run it here,
click it, and you'll notice that you get
some more errors. That is because you do
not have the Z image models installed
into your ComfyUI,
um or into your local
network pod that you have if you
followed the previous video. Again, link
in description for that. You definitely
should watch that. I show you exactly
how to get to this this point at the
beginning of the video that we just were
at, and um
it's just the best way to get everything
set up, so that way you can get directly
into getting this workflow working, if
that's what you want to do. So,
um you're going to see here that we're
missing a Z image uh turbo BF16 safe
tensors. We're missing a clip model, and
we're missing a VAE loader model. So,
that would be these right here.
Um and in the Discord,
you will notice that I have a section
here on commands that you can input into
your Jupyter Labs to download these
models directly from Hugging Face. Um
so,
no external downloads to your computer
involved. You don't need to take up all
of your precious uh hard drive space.
This can all be done through your
network pod that you have configured.
So, what we're going to do is we're
going to copy the
directory. We're going to change the
directory.
Go back here.
We're going to open a new terminal in
Jupyter Labs. So, just click the plus up
here on the tab. Open a new terminal.
And we are going to just copy and paste
everything from the Discord
right into here. So, you'll see that we
changed our directory to the diffusion
models
um
folder.
And then we are going to copy
everything else. So,
just put that in there,
and you'll see
that
the main Z image uh
turbo
model has begun downloading. So, this is
going to take a while, depending on
network speeds, etc., etc. So,
once that's done,
we will be back, and um
I'll show you how to get the rest of the
models installed.
Yo, guys. Real quick, right back to the
video. But first,
real quick, quick PSA. When adding funds
to RunPod, if you guys go to my
description of this video and use my
referral link, you will get $5 added to
whatever you add for your first purchase
through RunPod.
Also, that gives me $5, as well. So,
let's lock in together. Let's get this
money, and let's get this free money.
Also, if you guys need any run-throughs
or guides on things that you may not
understand, or you just can't get
something to work, and you really,
really want to get it to work, or you
want help creating workflows, or running
advanced workflows, using upscalers,
whatever it may be,
I offer super, super cheap lessons. I
just got into the creator space on
YouTube with all of this AI generation,
and so, you know, I don't really have a
viewer base. So,
I'm offering lessons on the most
advanced stuff that people are paying
thousands of dollars for. I'm offering
it for pennies on the dollar. So, if you
guys are interested, just reach out
through Discord. I'm always available.
Let me know.
All right. So, for demonstration
purposes, I stopped the download. I
already have this downloaded on my own
um personal network configuration. So,
I'm not going to download these models
again. I don't need to do that. I just
started up a new pod on a throwaway um
network, so that way I could show you
guys how to do this basically from
scratch. So, now we're going to do the
text encoders, which you can also find
right in the same spot in the Discord.
So, first we change our directory to the
text encoders folder, and then we're
going to
copy the wget command, and this will
start installing the text encoder.
Again, you'll see that there is a
download going here, and this is going
to take a while, too. This is a pretty
big file, but that's why you configure
the network, so that way the network
storage, so that way you can
save all of this, and then
from session to session, you don't have
to do this and reinstall these models
every single time.
Once you do this once, if you configure
the network storage, you will have it
ready to go. So, again, I'm just going
to stop this.
Um if it would stop, there we go.
And I'm going to pretend that that got
to 100%. Um it'll take, obviously, a lot
longer for you guys, so just pause the
video as you go through this. And we are
going to do the last model that we need,
which is the VAE. So, we are going to
copy again from the Discord the change
directory command to go into the VAE
folder.
And
we are going to copy then the wget
command
for the VAE.
And you should see this again, another
download. I'm going to stop it, like I
said. I'm going to move over to my
configured network that I already have
all this downloaded in, and
it should work exactly as yours will uh
once you have all of these installed,
and I will show you exactly how the
workflow works. All right. Back into
Comfy. Um
now that you have the models installed,
you should be able to see here
that you're able to click on them
when going through the list of models
that you have installed in each section.
So,
now that you can click on all of them,
there should be no more errors getting
thrown at you. And if there is,
there's a quick little cheat code I want
to show you guys. If you click run, and
you get errors, whatever pops up on that
error,
um you can just copy, and then paste it
right into Claude. Paste the error right
into here,
and say, "This is the error that I'm
getting when trying to run ComfyUI.
Here's my workflow." You can even drag
and drop the workflow that you're using
right into here, just the JSON file that
you would drag and drop into ComfyUI,
and then,
you know, say,
"These are your errors.
Here are the errors that I'm getting.
I am getting
when trying to run this workflow through
RunPod ComfyUI,
and he will tell you exactly what is
wrong, give you options for debugging
and fixing everything."
Huge cheat code, guys. Use LLMs. Use
these models. Use these language models
like Claude, which is great at coding,
great at debugging ComfyUI, and have him
fix all of your grievances, because it's
just the best way to do it. All right.
Once you have your models set, you'll
notice here that
you can load in LoRAs. So, if you have
character LoRAs, you can just load them
in right there.
And
if you read this,
if you are wanting to load your own
character style LoRAs into the workflow,
select your LoRAs in the window to the
left. So, you click LoRA, and
load whichever one you want.
And then, in the CR Prompt List node,
edit the pre-pen text to have your LoRA
trigger word. So, I'm going to select
one of my LoRAs here. Okay. Now that I
have one of my LoRAs set,
I'm going to come down to this CR Prompt
List node right here. And I'm going to
use the trigger word that I have
associated with my LoRA, or whatever
LoRA you're using.
And I'm just going to type it in,
followed by a comma and a space. Click
okay.
Now,
every single prompt
that is put into this text box here will
be prepended with this. So, my trigger
word will go in the beginning of each
one of these. So,
let me get rid of that real quick.
And I just want to show you how this
works with no Laura.
Now,
with this workflow,
this CEO prompt list is amazing because
normally you'd be able to put in one
positive prompt and
say that may be, you know,
a young Asian woman drinking a nice
coffee outside of a busy coffee shop.
You would just run the workflow with
that singular prompt, which is great.
But, for generating a large batches of
images, which these turbo
workflows or these turbo models, rather,
like Z image turbo, are great for
because they generate images so fast is
doing large batches. So, I can do as
many
prompts as I want to here. I just
separate them by the line. So, I'm going
to run this. This should give me three
images here. Um which you can set the
dimensions of the resolution. You can
set how many steps you want, which will
give you higher quality results with
higher steps. Um you can set negative
prompts that will run through each
iteration of
prompt. And I even put down here some
negative prompt tags that you can copy
and paste into the negative prompt box
if you want to avoid certain things. Um
there's lighting negatives, anatomy and
body negatives. And you can just, you
know, ask ChatGPT or whoever to give you
them more if you have problems with
generation. But, Z image is a great
model and I haven't really noticed that
many
uses for negative prompts.
But, I'm going to Okay, so I'm going to
run this.
All right, so here we go. Not even a
minute later, I have generated the three
images that I have prompts for.
Um we can take a look at them if we want
to. Let's take a look down here.
This is the young Asian woman drinking a
nice coffee outside of a busy coffee
shop. Nice.
We have a young Caucasian woman watering
her plants in her home garden. Amazing.
We have a young redhead woman on a jog
in the local park during the summer.
Great. Amazing. Now,
I want to show you how quick I can run
through a batch of, let's say, eight
prompts. So, I'm going to take these
and because I'm uncreative and lazy,
I am going to post them into my favorite
LLM
and say, "Generate me Generate me five
more prompts with a similar theme."
And we'll wait for him to answer.
Perfect.
And we'll take these
and just paste them right into there.
So,
now that we have those, I'm going to run
and I just want you guys to see how fast
these generate. You can see the first
image is done. Each case sampler with
the number following is which image it's
working on currently. So, I haven't set
the 10 steps, so it's usually going to
jump in iterations of 10% here. So,
we're already on image five.
Working on six now.
Seven.
And this should be the last one here.
Now,
let's change
this up here so that we have a neater
image feed.
There we go.
All of our prompts have come through.
You can see these images
are very real looking. They look
amazing. Um this image model is great. I
even like it better than Z image base at
this point. Z image base has been out
for a while now and I still prefer Z
image turbo.
It's just
better. I don't know.
A lot of people say it's a skill issue.
It may be. Maybe I just don't know how
to use Z image base, but
you can't beat the speed of Z image
turbo. Now,
one last thing that I'm going to do to
demonstrate how great this workflow is
is I'm going to plug in one of my custom
character words and I'm going to show
you exactly how that works. So,
Okay, so I've just gone back over to
Claude and told him, "Generate me 10
more, but do not describe ethnicity or
physical features. Just say a young
woman." So,
we have those prompts. So, I have 10 of
them. I'm going to come here. I'm going
to press control A to select all of the
prompts currently in this box. I'm going
to backspace. I'm going to paste
my prompts that I have just generated.
Notice that I have my Laura loaded up
here and I have my trigger word in the
prepended text. So, all I need to do.
Now, I have these 10 prompts ready to go
and I'm going to run that. All right.
Our batch of images has just finished.
Um you can see here if we expand our job
history, um it took 48 seconds for 10
images, which is on average, you know,
rounded up, 5 seconds per image. Can't
beat it. Here are the results. This is
the Laura that I loaded in. This is the
character that I created.
They look great. You can tell that the
consistency is maintained
throughout all of the images.
And yeah, so that's how you load your
Laura in.
Guys,
this is all you need for a text to image
workflow.
I'm telling you,
this is so much better than typing in
prompt after prompt after prompt
because you want to take advantage of
the speed of this model. You want to
take advantage of Z image turbo's turbo.
So, by doing that, the best way is to
load multiple prompts into one run of a
workflow so that way, you know, you're
not rerunning all the steps of the
workflow over and over and over again,
prompt by prompt, by prompt, by prompt.
Um
a few things to note. If you want to
mess with the sampler name and the
scheduler, this will change certain
aspects of the generation. Um certain
samplers and schedulers are
better run with lower steps. So, what I
have it to What I have it set to by
default is Euler with beta 57. This is
good for a low step iteration. So, 10
steps with this combination is all you
need. You'll get great results. Um
great consistency through your Laura's.
And
yeah, I mean, that's really it for this,
guys. That's, you know, as simple as it
gets. It's what you get. So, if you like
the video, please like. Please
subscribe. Join the Discord. If you have
any questions, feel free to ask in
there. I'm always willing to help. And
thank you for watching.